<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Team on LABHDUFBA</title>
    <link>//localhost:37865/team/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Team on LABHDUFBA</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:37865/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Leonardo F. Nascimento</title>
      <link>//localhost:37865/team/1_leonardo-nascimento/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:37865/team/1_leonardo-nascimento/</guid>
      <description>I am a Chemical Technician, graduated in Psychology, hold a master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Sociology (2007), PhD in Sociology and the coordinator of the Digital Humanities Laboratory at UFBA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Brasil</title>
      <link>//localhost:37865/team/2_eric-brasil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:37865/team/2_eric-brasil/</guid>
      <description>Professor of the undergraduate courses in History and Humanities at the Institute of Humanities and Languages at the University for the International Integration of Afro-Brazilian Lusophony (IHLM/UNILAB), Malês campus, Bahia, Brazil (2017 - current).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rosana Moore</title>
      <link>//localhost:37865/team/3_rosana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:37865/team/3_rosana/</guid>
      <description>Rosana Silva Chagas, currently Rosana Silva Moore Wedderburn, holds a PhD (2019) and a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree (2012) in Sociology from the Graduate Program of the Institute of Social and Political Studies (IESP) at the Rio de Janeiro State University (UERJ), and a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Sociology from the Federal University of Bahia (2007).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Letícia Cesarino</title>
      <link>//localhost:37865/team/4_leticia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:37865/team/4_leticia/</guid>
      <description>Letícia Cesarino was born in Belo Horizonte in 1979, She graduated in Social Sciences from UFMG in 2003 and completed her Master&amp;rsquo;s in Social Anthropology at UNB in 2006, She earned her PhD in Anthropology from UC Berkeley in 2013, conducting field research in Brazil, Mali, Ghana, and Burkina Faso.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bruno Durães</title>
      <link>//localhost:37865/team/5_bruno/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:37865/team/5_bruno/</guid>
      <description>Ph.D. in Social Sciences (Unicamp-2011), with a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Sociology (Unicamp-2006), a degree in Social Sciences (2003), and a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Sociology (2004) from the Federal University of Bahia (UFBA).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarssio Barreto</title>
      <link>//localhost:37865/team/6_tarssio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:37865/team/6_tarssio/</guid>
      <description>Graduated in Sanitary and Environmental Engineering and holds a Master&amp;rsquo;s in Environment, Water, and Sanitation, Currently, I develop data-driven products at BIT Analytics, I have a strong interest in partnerships for innovation and data-oriented product development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alan Mocellim</title>
      <link>//localhost:37865/team/7_alan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:37865/team/7_alan/</guid>
      <description>Associate Professor in the Department of Sociology at the Federal University of Bahia (UFBA) and the Graduate Program in Social Sciences at the same institution, He holds degrees in Social Sciences from the Federal University of Santa Catarina (UFSC) and Psychology from UFBA, a Master&amp;rsquo;s in Political Sociology from UFSC, and a Ph.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ícaro Bernardes dos Santos Coutinho</title>
      <link>//localhost:37865/team/8_icaro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:37865/team/8_icaro/</guid>
      <description>I am a data scientist with a strong focus on data analysis, modeling, and visualization; I have experience in academic research, starting from high school, and client projects, which I have recently acquired.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graziela de Souza Teixeira</title>
      <link>//localhost:37865/team/9_grazi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:37865/team/9_grazi/</guid>
      <description>Currently, a student of Anthropology at the Federal University of Santa Catarina (UFSC) since 2019, I hold a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Business Administration from the University of Vale do Paraíba (UNIVAP, 1998) and a postgraduate degree in Accounting and Financial Administration from Fundação Armando Álvares Penteado (FAAP, 2000).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leonardo Thibau</title>
      <link>//localhost:37865/team/10_thibau/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:37865/team/10_thibau/</guid>
      <description>Undergraduate student in Social Sciences, and Bachelor of Humanities Interdisciplinary Studies at UFBA (2020), PIBIC scholarship recipient at the Laboratory of Science, Technology, and Society - LABCTS, Was a member of the Seminar on Introduction to Psychoanalytic Theory - SIPSI (2019).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruan Arthur Lima Santos</title>
      <link>//localhost:37865/team/11_arthur/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:37865/team/11_arthur/</guid>
      <description>Currently, an undergraduate student of Social Sciences at the Federal University of Bahia (UFBA), I have research interests in Epistemology, Gender and Identity Studies, Sociology of Religion, Sociology of Crime, and the Far Right.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
