<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Team on LABHDUFBA</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/authors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Team on LABHDUFBA</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Leonardo F. Nascimento</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/1_leonardo-nascimento/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/1_leonardo-nascimento/</guid>
      <description>I am a Chemical Technician, graduated in Psychology, hold a master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Sociology (2007), PhD in Sociology and the coordinator of the Digital Humanities Laboratory at UFBA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Brasil</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/2_eric-brasil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/2_eric-brasil/</guid>
      <description>Professor at the Institute of Humanities and Languages at the University for the International Integration of Afro-Brazilian Lusophony (IHLM/UNILAB); PhD (2016) and MA (2011) in History from the Federal Fluminense University; Managing Editor of Programming Historian in Portuguese.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rosana Moore</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/3_rosana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/3_rosana/</guid>
      <description>Rosana Silva Chagas, currently Rosana Silva Moore Wedderburn, holds a PhD (2019) and a master&amp;rsquo;s degree (2012) in Sociology from the Postgraduate Program at the Institute of Social and Political Studies (IESP) of the State University of Rio de Janeiro (UERJ).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Letícia Cesarino</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/4_leticia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/4_leticia/</guid>
      <description>Professor and researcher at UFSC, she graduated in Social Sciences from UFMG in 2003 and completed her Master&amp;rsquo;s in Social Anthropology at UNB in 2006; Obtained her PhD in Anthropology from UC Berkeley in 2013, conducting field research in Brazil, Mali, Ghana, and Burkina Faso.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juciane Pereira de Jesus</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/5_juci/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/5_juci/</guid>
      <description>Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s in Social Sciences (2022) from the Federal University of Bahia (UFBA), undergraduate student in Sociology (re-admission/UFBA), and Master&amp;rsquo;s student in the Graduate Program in Social Sciences (PPGCS/UFBA).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarssio Barreto</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/6_tarssio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/6_tarssio/</guid>
      <description>Graduated in Sanitary and Environmental Engineering with a Master&amp;rsquo;s in Environment, Water, and Sanitation; Currently, develop data-driven products at BIT Analytics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alan Mocellim</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/7_alan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/7_alan/</guid>
      <description>Associate Professor in the Department of Sociology at the Federal University of Bahia (UFBA) and the Graduate Program in Social Sciences at the same institution; Holds a PhD in Sociology from the University of São Paulo (USP) and serves as vice-coordinator of the Digital Humanities Laboratory at UFBA (LABHD) and member of the Cultural Psychology Research Group (CULTS).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ricardo Sodré Andrade</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/8_ric/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/8_ric/</guid>
      <description>Leader of the Research Group on Culture, Representation, and Digital Information (CRIDI) at the Federal University of Bahia (UFBA); Holds a Master’s in Information Science from the Graduate Program in Information Science at UFBA (PPGCI/UFBA) and a Bachelor’s degree in Archival Science from UFBA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graziela de Souza Teixeira</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/9_grazi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/9_grazi/</guid>
      <description>Currently an Anthropology student at the Federal University of Santa Catarina (UFSC) since 2019; Hold a Bachelor’s degree in Business Administration from the University of Vale do Paraíba (UNIVAP, 1998) and a postgraduate degree in Accounting and Financial Management from Fundação Armando Álvares Penteado (FAAP, 2000).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leonardo Thibau</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/10_thibau/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/10_thibau/</guid>
      <description>Master&amp;rsquo;s student in Sociology (PPGCS/UFBA). Undergraduate in Social Sciences and a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s in Humanities from UFBA (2020), was a PIBIC scholarship holder at the Laboratory of Science, Technology, and Society - LABCTS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruan Arthur Lima Santos</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/11_arthur/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/11_arthur/</guid>
      <description>Currently, pursuing a degree in Social Sciences at the Federal University of Bahia (UFBA).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jorge Henrique Silvestre Barbosa</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/12_jorge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/12_jorge/</guid>
      <description>I graduated in Social Sciences and hold a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Sociology; I am currently a PhD candidate in the Graduate Program in Social Sciences at the Federal University of Bahia (PPGCS/UFBA).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bruno Durães</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/13_bruno/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/13_bruno/</guid>
      <description>Associate Professor of Sociology at UFRJ (Department of Sociology/IFCS); Coordinator of the Digital Humanities Laboratory at UFRJ; Holds a PhD in Social Sciences (Unicamp-2011).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonatã Bittencourt</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/14_jonata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/14_jonata/</guid>
      <description>I am conducting doctoral research on Innovation Policies guiding the management of actions and projects in publicly owned ICTs, focusing on a civic-democratic approach to Social Innovation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ícaro Bernardes dos Santos Coutinho</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/15_icaro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/15_icaro/</guid>
      <description>Data scientist with a strong focus on data analysis, modeling, and visualization; Has experience in academic research and client-oriented projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indianara Lima Silva</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/16_indianara/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/16_indianara/</guid>
      <description>Indianara Silva is a Full Professor in the Physics Department at UEFS and a member of the Graduate Program in Science Teaching, Philosophy, and History (UFBA-UEFS); Completed her postdoctoral studies at the Department of the History of Science at Harvard University and was elected History of Physics Editor for the Revista Brasileira de Ensino de Física in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desirée Vitória Vigas Melo</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/17_desiree/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/17_desiree/</guid>
      <description>Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Humanities (2023), undergraduate student in Social Sciences. Interested in sociology of religion, misinformation, and digital sociology; She was a teaching assistant for the ACCS Pluralism and Religious Rights (2022), and volunteered at the CRH - Center for Studies and Research in Humanities at UFBA (2023); She was a researcher at LABCTS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Romero</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/18_romero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/18_romero/</guid>
      <description>Holds a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Sociology and a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Social Sciences from Universidade Estadual de Campinas (1996); has experience in the field of Sociology, with an emphasis on the Fundamentals of Sociology, currently serves as a Professor of Sociology at the higher education level at Instituto Federal da Bahia in Salvador.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vítor Mussa</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/19_vitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/19_vitor/</guid>
      <description>Software engineer and computational social scientist; I have more than 3 years of professional and scientific experience working with Python building the backend of web apps, data pipelines, and data platforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Maia</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/20_eric-maia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/20_eric-maia/</guid>
      <description>Historian graduated from the Federal Fluminense University (UFF); Postgraduate in Technologies Applied to Education; Master&amp;rsquo;s student in the Graduate Program in History at UFF; main areas of expertise include Brazilian History, Contemporary History, Visual History, and Present-Day History.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alisson Magalhães Soares</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/21_alisson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/21_alisson/</guid>
      <description>Bachelor in Social Sciences, specialist in the History of Science, Master&amp;rsquo;s and PhD in Sociology at UFMG, Post-Doctorate in Political Science at UFPE.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matheus da Costa Martins</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/22_matheus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/22_matheus/</guid>
      <description>Born in Santos, São Paulo, he is an undergraduate student in Social Sciences at the Federal University of Santa Catarina; Additionally, he is a Scientific Initiation scholarship holder (PIBIC).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daniel de Sena Bastos</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/23_daniel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/23_daniel/</guid>
      <description>Undergraduate in Science, Technology, and Innovation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jéfte Batista de Oliveira</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/24_jefte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/24_jefte/</guid>
      <description>Bachelor in Social Sciences from the Federal University of Bahia (UFBA); Currently, a master&amp;rsquo;s student in the Graduate Program in Social Sciences (PPGCS) at UFBA and a Sociology teacher for the Department of Education of the State of Bahia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaime Cativa</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/25_jaime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/25_jaime/</guid>
      <description>Student representative of the Interdisciplinary Bachelor’s Degree in Humanities at the Institute of Humanities and Letters of the University for International Integration of the Afro-Brazilian Lusophony (IHLM/UNILAB).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gilberto Sassi</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/26_gilberto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/26_gilberto/</guid>
      <description>Data Scientist and Natural Language Processing (NLP) specialist at the Department of Statistics of the Institute of Mathematics and Statistics at UFBA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gabriel Andrade</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/27_gabriel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/27_gabriel/</guid>
      <description>Currently, pursuing a degree in Computer Engineering at Federal University of Bahia (UFBA); I work as a Software Engineer with a large experience in Software Development using modern technologies as Python, Node, PHP, Docker and so on.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
