<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Team on LABHDUFBA</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/authors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Team on LABHDUFBA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Leonardo F. Nascimento</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/1_leonardo-nascimento/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/1_leonardo-nascimento/</guid>
      <description>I am a Chemical Technician, graduated in Psychology, hold a master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Sociology (2007), PhD in Sociology and the coordinator of the Digital Humanities Laboratory at UFBA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Brasil</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/2_eric-brasil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/2_eric-brasil/</guid>
      <description>Professor at the Institute of Humanities and Languages at the University for the International Integration of Afro-Brazilian Lusophony (IHLM/UNILAB); PhD (2016) and MA (2011) in History from the Federal Fluminense University; Managing Editor of Programming Historian in Portuguese.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rosana Moore</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/3_rosana/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/3_rosana/</guid>
      <description>Rosana Silva Chagas, currently Rosana Silva Moore Wedderburn, holds a PhD (2019) and a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree (2012) in Sociology from the Graduate Program of the Institute of Social and Political Studies (IESP) at the Rio de Janeiro State University (UERJ), and a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Sociology from the Federal University of Bahia (2007); She has experience in the field of Sociology, with an emphasis on racial relations, urban sociology, and criminology, focusing primarily on the topics of violence, genocide, homicides, and racial inequalities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Letícia Cesarino</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/4_leticia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/4_leticia/</guid>
      <description>Letícia Cesarino was born in Belo Horizonte in 1979, She graduated in Social Sciences from UFMG in 2003 and completed her Master&amp;rsquo;s in Social Anthropology at UNB in 2006, She earned her PhD in Anthropology from UC Berkeley in 2013, conducting field research in Brazil, Mali, Ghana, and Burkina Faso; She is a professor and researcher at UFSC, specializing in the social studies of science and technology, with a recent focus on digital anthropology; She co-coordinates a project on disinformation on Telegram with UFBA&amp;rsquo;s Digital Humanities Laboratory and InternetLab; She also writes for Carta Capital and Jacobin Brasil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juciane P. de Jesus</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/5_juci/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/5_juci/</guid>
      <description>Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Social Sciences (2022) from the Federal University of Bahia (UFBA), undergraduate student in Sociology (re-entry/UFBA) and master&amp;rsquo;s student in the postgraduate program in Social Sciences (PPGCS/UFBA), member and researcher at the Laboratory of Digital Humanities (LabHD/UFBA); Research topics include Digital Sociology, Digital Research Methods, Social Networks, Health-related Disinformation, and the Far-right in Brazil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarssio Barreto</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/6_tarssio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/6_tarssio/</guid>
      <description>Graduated in Sanitary and Environmental Engineering and holds a Master&amp;rsquo;s in Environment, Water, and Sanitation, Currently, I develop data-driven products at BIT Analytics, I have a strong interest in partnerships for innovation and data-oriented product development; Additionally, I consider myself a data activist and am open to projects with Institutes and Foundations involving socio-environmental issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alan Mocellim</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/7_alan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/7_alan/</guid>
      <description>Associate Professor in the Department of Sociology at the Federal University of Bahia (UFBA) and the Graduate Program in Social Sciences at the same institution, He holds degrees in Social Sciences from the Federal University of Santa Catarina (UFSC) and Psychology from UFBA, a Master&amp;rsquo;s in Political Sociology from UFSC, and a PhD in Sociology from the University of São Paulo (USP); He is the deputy coordinator of UFBA&amp;rsquo;s Digital Humanities Laboratory (LABHD) and a member of the Cultural Psychology Research Group (CULTS).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ricardo Sodré Andrade</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/8_ric/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/8_ric/</guid>
      <description>Leader of the Research Group on Culture, Representation, and Digital Information (CRIDI) at the Federal University of Bahia (UFBA); Holds a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Information Science from the Graduate Program in Information Science at UFBA (PPGCI/UFBA) and a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Archival Science from UFBA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graziela de Souza Teixeira</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/9_grazi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/9_grazi/</guid>
      <description>Currently, a student of Anthropology at the Federal University of Santa Catarina (UFSC) since 2019, I hold a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Business Administration from the University of Vale do Paraíba (UNIVAP, 1998) and a postgraduate degree in Accounting and Financial Administration from Fundação Armando Álvares Penteado (FAAP, 2000); With twelve years of experience in the traditional financial market, my research interests include digital anthropology, blockchain data infrastructures, digital currencies, and emerging forms of identity and social organization in Web3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leonardo Thibau</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/10_thibau/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/10_thibau/</guid>
      <description>Undergraduate student in Social Sciences, and Bachelor of Humanities Interdisciplinary Studies at UFBA (2020), PIBIC scholarship recipient at the Laboratory of Science, Technology, and Society - LABCTS; Was a member of the Seminar on Introduction to Psychoanalytic Theory - SIPSI (2019); Has experience in education, with an internship at Lua Nova School (2019) and in the Teaching Initiation Program - PIBID (2023).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruan Arthur Lima Santos</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/11_arthur/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/11_arthur/</guid>
      <description>Currently, an undergraduate student of Social Sciences at the Federal University of Bahia (UFBA), I have research interests in Epistemology, Gender and Identity Studies, Sociology of Religion, Sociology of Crime, and the Far Right.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jorge Henrique Silvestre Barbosa</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/12_jorge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/12_jorge/</guid>
      <description>I graduated in Social Sciences and hold a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Sociology; I am currently a PhD candidate in the Graduate Program in Social Sciences at the Federal University of Bahia (PPGCS/UFBA), I have been a member of LABHDUFBA since 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bruno Durães</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/13_bruno/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/13_bruno/</guid>
      <description>Ph.D. in Social Sciences (Unicamp-2011), with a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Sociology (Unicamp-2006), a degree in Social Sciences (2003), and a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Sociology (2004) from the Federal University of Bahia (UFBA); Associate Professor of Sociology at UFRJ (Department of Sociology/IFCS); Coordinator of the Laboratory of Digital Humanities at UFRJ.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonatã Bittencourt</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/14_jonata/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/14_jonata/</guid>
      <description>I am conducting doctoral research on Innovation Policies that guide the management of actions and projects in public law ICTs, with a focus on a civic-democratic approach to Social Innovation; My other research interests include Sociological and Post-Colonial Perspectives in Science, Technology, and Innovation (ST&amp;amp;I), the role of Digital Humanities in producing innovations within public law ICTs, and the interplay of Ethics, Citizenship, and Human Rights in ST&amp;amp;I.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ícaro Bernardes dos Santos Coutinho</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/15_icaro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/15_icaro/</guid>
      <description>I am a data scientist with a strong focus on data analysis, modeling, and visualization; I have experience in academic research, starting from high school, and client projects, which I have recently acquired; My work spans a broad spectrum, including optimization using heuristic methods, loss analysis in the blood derivatives supply chain, and impact assessment of social projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indianara Lima Silva</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/16_indianara/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/16_indianara/</guid>
      <description>Indianara Silva is a Full Professor in the Physics Department at UEFS and a member of the Graduate Program in Science Teaching, Philosophy, and History (UFBA-UEFS); Completed her postdoctoral studies at the Department of the History of Science at Harvard University and was elected History of Physics Editor for the Revista Brasileira de Ensino de Física in 2024; Received the Carolina Nemes Award from the Brazilian Physics Society in 2022 and conducted research at prestigious institutions such as Harvard, MIT, and the Royal Society.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desirée Vitória Vigas Melo</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/17_desiree/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/17_desiree/</guid>
      <description>Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Humanities (2023), undergraduate student in Social Sciences. Interested in sociology of religion, misinformation, and digital sociology; She was a teaching assistant for the ACCS Pluralism and Religious Rights (2022), and volunteered at the CRH - Center for Studies and Research in Humanities at UFBA (2023); Currently, she is a researcher at LABHD and LABCTS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Romero</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/18_romero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/18_romero/</guid>
      <description>Holds a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Sociology and a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Social Sciences from Universidade Estadual de Campinas (1996); has experience in the field of Sociology, with an emphasis on the Fundamentals of Sociology, currently serves as a Professor of Sociology at the higher education level at Instituto Federal da Bahia in Salvador.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vítor Mussa</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/19_vitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/19_vitor/</guid>
      <description>Software engineer and computational social scientist; I have more than 3 years of professional and scientific experience working with Python building the backend of web apps, data pipelines, and data platforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Maia</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/20_eric-maia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/20_eric-maia/</guid>
      <description>Historian graduated from the Federal Fluminense University (UFF); Postgraduate in Technologies Applied to Education; Master&amp;rsquo;s student in the Graduate Program in History at UFF; main areas of expertise include Brazilian History, Contemporary History, Visual History, and Present-Day History.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alisson Magalhães Soares</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/21_alisson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/21_alisson/</guid>
      <description>Bachelor in Social Sciences, specialist in the History of Science, Master&amp;rsquo;s and PhD in Sociology at UFMG, Post-Doctorate in Political Science at UFPE; Currently interested in disinformation, conspiracy theories, Computational Social Sciences, text analysis/text mining, and Natural Language Processing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matheus da Costa Martins</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/22_matheus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/22_matheus/</guid>
      <description>Born in Santos, São Paulo, he is an undergraduate student in Social Sciences at the Federal University of Santa Catarina; Additionally, he is a Scientific Initiation scholarship holder (PIBIC) under the supervision of professor Dr Letícia Cesarino, focusing on the thematic area of the far-right and social networks; He participates as a researcher at the Laboratory of Digital Humanities (LABHD/UFBA) and at the University Laboratory of Politics, Rights, Conflicts, and Anthropology (LUPA/UFSC).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daniel de Sena Bastos</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/23_daniel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/23_daniel/</guid>
      <description>Undergraduate in Science, Technology, and Innovation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jéfte Batista de Oliveira</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/authors/24_jefte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/authors/24_jefte/</guid>
      <description>Bachelor in Social Sciences from the Federal University of Bahia (UFBA).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
